Oh, hey, Rach.
Hi.
Hey.
Happy Valentine's Day.
Oh, you, too.
Oh, so how's it going
living over at Ross's?
It's good
except he makes us watch
The Discovery Channel
all day long.
Did you know that something
really boring
happened to someone really ugly
in the Middle Ages?
Oh, thank you.
I'll see you
guys later.
Okay.
Bye.
There's one lucky
to-go cup of coffee.
( sighs )
Honey, I wish you
would get over her.
I hate seeing you
like this.
Is there anything
I can do for you?
Do you want to look
down my top?
Thanks, but maybe
later, okay?
Oh, Gunther.
Could I get a scone?
Do you want anything?
You know what I want?
I want a lot of things.
I want to be with the woman
I love on Valentine's Day
and I want her
to love me back
and I want just
one moment of relief
from the gut-wrenching pain
of knowing
that's never going to happen.
We have red bagels.
Oh, okay.
♪ So no one told you
life was gonna be this way ♪
♪ Your job's a joke,
you're broke ♪
♪ Your love life's D.O.A. ♪
♪ It's like you're always
stuck in second gear ♪
♪ When it hasn't been
your day, your week ♪
♪ Your month,
or even your year ♪
♪ But I'll be there for you ♪
♪ 'Cause you're there
for me, too. ♪
How does Mona feel
about you two
living together?
Oh, I'm actually on my
way to tell her right now.
Yeah, she's been away all
week visiting her parents
but she'll be cool.
I mean, she's been
so supportive.
She-she even got the baby
a tiny T-shirt
that says, "Fossils
are my friends."
Ugh.
Come on, Mona, don't kiss ass.
So, I'm going
to take off.
All right. Oh.
Shoot. Oh, shoot.
Uh, Rachel wanted
to see this tape.
What is it?
It's a video
of my friend giving birth.
Could you just bring it back
to your apartment?
All right.
"Candy and Cookie"?
Yeah.
Candy's the mother,
Cookie's the daughter.
The father's name
is also Cookie.
Why am I friends
with these people?
Phoebe, come here.
I want to show you something
in the bathroom.
Oh, Monica, grow up.
Hey, what have you got
behind your back?
Nothing. Just... Just something
I want to get
Phoebe's opinion on
for Valentine's Day.
You don't want my opinion?
Not really.
Oh, come on, I'm your
older brother-- ask me.
Oh, okay, big brother.
Which one of these do you think
would make your
little sister look hotter
so your best friend
would want to do her?
The red one.
( door opening )
Hey.
Look, I know you've been
really depressed lately
so I've brought someone
over to cheer you up.
Right outside this door
is a real, live, furry playmate.
No, I'm not sleeping
with your friend Jane again.
He-hee!
Hey, a dog.
Oh, hi.
Who, you got to admit,
looks a lot like Jane.
This is the happiest
dog in the world.
I borrowed him
from my friend Wendy
so you can keep him
till he cheers you up
and he will cheer you up.
Thanks so much, Pheebs.
We are going to have
so much fun, yes, we are.
Oh, not that kind of fun.
Happy Valentine's!
Hey!
I'll be right out.
I'm slipping
into something
a little less
comfortable
and a little
more slutty.
"Candy and Cookie"?
Monica got me porn?
Girl-on-girl porn?
She really must love me!
( woman breathing hard )
MAN:
Yeah, just relax.
I love you, St. Valentine.
( woman breathing, moaning )
Whoa, whoa, that's not pretty.
MAN:
Now, push.
( woman yelling )
Worst porn ever,
worst porn ever!
( screaming ):
Oh, make it stop!
I am trying.
Get the ball. Get the ball.
Ready? Get the ball.
Well, you're cute,
but you're not too smart.
Did I just throw this?
Hi.
I accidentally
packed these
with my stuff.
( gasps )
Who is this?
That's Phoebe's
friend's dog. Yeah.
I don't know what is real name
is, but I call him Mozzarella.
Oh... You are so cute.
I wish I could
play with you more
but I've got to go to work.
I hope I stop
talking like this
before my marketing
meeting, yes, I do.
Yes, I do.
Bye-bye, Joey.
I seriously can't stop it.
Come here. Hey.
Hey...
That's Rachel.
She's the one
who used to live here.
Might as well
be honest with you--
We love her
but we can't have her.
I really miss her.
Well, hey,
you understand, right?
You're a guy.
Well... you used to be.
So, what do you think?
I've still got it.
Why did you
get me this?
What is it?
It's yelling... bleeding...
dilating...
Oh, the dilating.
Is this the video of
the baby being born?
Sweetie, this is Phoebe's.
Why were you
even watching it?
I thought maybe you got me porn
for Valentine's Day.
Chandler, if you
thought I was
going to get you porn
for Valentine's Day...
You were right.
Apparently it's
about a young girl
who moves to the big city
you know, in
search of stardom
but ends up having sex
with a lot of guys.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, it got four stars.
Oh, wait a minute--
those aren't stars.
Anyway, you want
to take a look?
Well...
I'm not really
in a sexy mood right now.
Hey, what's going on?
Well...
Remember the first time
you saw Jaws?
Mm-hmm.
How long it took
to go back in the water?
Chandler, we can't let this
tape wreck Valentine's Day.
You don't know.
You didn't see it.
Childbirth, it-it's
a natural thing.
It's beautiful.
Oh, b-beautiful? Really?
Oh, really? You think
this is beautiful?
( screaming )
Oh, my God. No wonder
my mother hates me.
See, honey, there's...
Don't touch me.
Hi.
Hey.
So? How was Atlantic City?
Good.
Yeah?
I brought you
back a present.
What? Oh, come on.
You didn't have to...
salt water taffy?!
Thanks.
You know,
it's interesting.
Most people think this
is made with seawater
but it's actually made with,
uh... salted fresh water.
That's not interesting.
I think it's
interesting.
I do, too.
I missed you.
Oh, me, too.
So, how was your week?
Oh, it was good,
it was good.
Actually, the baby
started kicking.
How exciting.
Yeah, I know. Oh...
It was amazing.
The sad thing is,
I wasn't around
when it happened
for the first time.
Oh, no.
Yeah, I know.
I was missing out
on all this other stuff, too
so Joey suggested
Rachel move in with me.
Yeah, right.
What?
Joey cracks me up.
It's like, "Yeah,
why don't you
"have your ex-wife
move in with you?
That wouldn't be
awkward at all."
Huh.
Hey, could you imagine?
I go away for
a few days.
I come back, and
my boyfriend
is living with some
woman he got pregnant.
So, what did
you tell him?
Mm-mmm-mmm.
How could you
not tell Mona
that Rachel
is living with you?
I don't know.
She seemed to think it
was such a crazy idea.
Plus, she, uh...
she got me taffy.
Taffy? Really?
I've never had any.
Ever?
My mother was too busy
planning her suicide
to provide
saltwater treats.
Thank you.
So, what, are you just
never going to tell her?
Oh, no, no, no.
I will.
I just want to
butter her up first.
I'm going to take her
to an amazing
Valentine's dinner
do all this
romantic stuff
and then,
just when she thinks
I'm the best boyfriend
in the world
then I'm going
to tell her
that my pregnant
ex-girlfriend
is living with me.
If I haven't said it before
she's a lucky, lucky lady.
So where you going to...?
What the mother of crap
is up with this stuff?
Oh, God!
Is it gum? Is it food?
What... what's the deal?
Oh, it's nice.
May I try a pink one?
So, between her
and me being friends
and her history with Ross
it just isn't going to happen.
It would be like you
falling in love with a cat.
Hey.
Hey, Buddy.
How's my
favorite dog, huh?
favorite dog?
You're subdued.
Did you give him a beer?
No.
Will you excuse us?
We need to talk for a moment.
Yeah, sure. Go...
Oh, me. Right.
He's miserable.
What happened to him?
Nothing.
Just talked
about stuff.
What stuff?
Rachel stuff.
Oh, Joey,
you bummed him out.
This was the happiest
dog in the world.
He spends
half a day with you
and look at him.
He's breathing.
Okay, I'm going
to take him back
to Wendy's.
No, no, no. He's fine.
Look, look, look.
Here's your ball.
Get the ball.
Get your ball.
Get your ball!
Get your ball! Get...
My God, what have
I done to you?
Huh? I broke the dog.
I broke the dog!
Well, I'm going
to pick up Mona.
What have you got
going on tonight?
Oh, I got big Valentine's plans.
I got my Chinese food on the way
and the rest
of your saltwater taffy.
You know, it's interesting.
Most people think that's made
with seawater, when, in fact...
Ross, we actually watched
the documentary together.
( knocking on door )
Oop! My Chinese food.
I'll get my cash.
Mona?
You're, uh...
What are...? Hi.
Hi.
What are you doing here?
I'm supposed
to pick you up.
Change of plans.
I made you a special
Valentine's dinner.
Surprise!
( yells )
Oh. Hey, Mona.
Hi. Hi. Hi, Rachel.
What's she doing here?
I have no idea.
Um... I'll
be watching TV
if anybody needs me.
Seriously,
what is she doing here?
Uh... you know, lately
she just likes
hanging out here.
Why?
I think she's lonely.
Okay, but it's
Valentine's Day.
Can't we just
ask her to go?
Well, no, no.
She's way
too emotional.
And, by emotional,
I mean...
( doorbell rings )
I'm not here.
That's just my Chinese food.
Oh, my God. She has
food delivered here?
Yes. She's...
she's emotional
but... but ballsy.
You know what I'm going to do?
I'm going to get in my sweats
and eat this in bed.
And you thought she was
going to be in our way.
So, okay,
why don't you
open the champagne
and I will
be right back.
I've got
a surprise for you.
You got another ex-wife
back there?
Oh... you...
please start drinking.
I just came
to grab the phone.
Oh, Rachel, wait. Hey.
Um... I hope
you don't take
this the wrong way
but... but, um...
what are you doing?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Do you need the phone?
No. No. Listen
Ross is too nice
to say anything
but this
is his apartment
and we... we got to
have some boundaries
so why don't you just
go back to your place
and give us
some privacy.
But, Mona,
I... I live here.
Happy Valentine's Day!
Or something
to remember me by.
How long has
it been this time?
90 seconds.
That's better.
90 seconds
is a long time
not to think about it
except all I did
was think about it.
I know. It haunts me.
Up till now,
the worst thing I ever saw
was my father
doing tequila shots
off the naked houseboy.
After this,
I would gladly
make that
my screen saver.
We have
to get past this.
Why don't we just
get rid of the tape
and pretend it
never existed.
I could do that.
All right.
Okay, now all we got to do
is get rid of this chair.
( knocking on door )
Oh, thank God!
Oh, I know!
Come in.
Hi. I'm so sorry
to barge in on your Valentine
but I had to get away
from all the yelling.
Mona is dumping Ross.
Oh, my God.
Poor Ross.
Oh, great.
We have to watch him
do yoga in his underwear
but for this
he closes the drapes.
Rach, you know
that birthing tape
that you wanted to see?
It's here.
Oh, and we
should warn you
before you watch it...
Don't watch it.
Why? You saw it? Is it scary?
Well, let's just say
that it's ironic
how footage
of someone being born
can make you want
to kill yourself.
Well... well, now, wait.
I'm all freaked out.
Come on. You guys
will watch it with me.
No, but I will
leave a sweater
that smells like me
right next to you.
Come on, seriously, you guys.
You're not going
to make me watch this alone.
She's right.
Of course not.
Honey, get the tape.
This reminds me of a very
specific part of the tape.
Okay...
here we go.
Okay.
( clears throat )
Ooh, my!
( woman screaming )
Oh, why is that baby
torturing that woman?!
Why have I seen this thing
three times?
It's still beautiful.
Ah! It's horrible!
I know! I know!
I'm so sorry for you!
Oh, my God!
You guys... you guys, look!
What? What?
Did her ass explode?
No. The baby's out.
Look. It's a girl.
Oh, look at those
little fingers and toes.
And look how happy
the mom is now.
Oh, Rach...
Oh, screw you guys!
You don't have to do it.
Hey.
What's up?
Uh... Mona
just dumped me.
Oh, man,
I'm sorry. Why?
Well, with everything
that's been going on lately
I haven't exactly
been the perfect boyfriend.
You know, I mean,
I didn't tell her
I got Rachel pregnant.
Then I gave her a key
to my apartment
and then I had
the locks changed.
And then...
I lied to her about
Rachel moving in with me.
In a way, I...
I actually judge her
for not breaking up
with me sooner, you know?
Still, that
really sucks, man.
Especially
on Valentine's Day.
Yeah. Wait a minute.
What are you doing here?
Joey Tribbiani without
a date on Valentine's Day?
What's going on, man?
Girl trouble?
Sort of. Yeah.
Really?
You don't have
to seem so happy
about it.
Oh, sorry.
Well, look,
maybe I can help.
Oh, I... I don't...
Hey, hey, hey,
whatever it is
I am sure
it has happened to me.
You know
actually, once... once
I got dumped during sex.
So, anyway...
so what is it?
Oh, forget about it.
It's no big deal.
Hey, come on, Joey.
What is it?
It's nothing.
Hey, hey, it's me.
Why can't you tell me?
Okay. Uh... sit down.
Um...
There's this woman
that I like... a lot...
but, uh... it can't happen.
She's not a Tribbiani?
No!
I knew it.
So, uh... so is she,
uh... someone from work?
Yes.
Well, uh... does she like you?
Sometimes I think
maybe she could.
But it doesn't matter
because I can't do anything
about it.
Why not?
It's complicated.
Um... she was with this
other guy... for a long time--
someone from work, too--
and, uh, I could never do that
to the guy, you know
'cause we're
really good friends.
Okay, so this... this guy
she used to go out with...
Is, uh...
is he still in love with her?
No. I don't think so.
Okay, um...
Is he a good guy?
Yeah, he's the best.
Then talk to him.
He might be fine with it.
Oh, I don't know.
Joey, come on.
It's worth finding out.
I mean, if you really like her.
I do... so much I can't
stop thinking about her.
I can't sleep, I...
Okay, Joey, you know what?
You... you have to go for it.
How often does
this happen to you, huh?
I mean, you owe it
to yourself.
Here's your warm milk.
I'm-I'm going to get...
I'm going to put
the bourbon in it at home.
Yeah.
Anyway, seriously
just... just talk
to the guy, okay?
And let me know
how it goes.
It's Rachel.
and you need to be prepared.
Now, you're going to make
yourself watch the whole thing.
Just do it.
WOMAN:
I came to the big city
to become a star.
I'll do anything
to make that happen.
MAN:
Anything?
RACHEL:
Huh. Maybe it starts
with how she gets pregnant.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org